learn-texas-holdem.com 2019-07-06

# Privacy Policy for PokerListings.com | Online Poker Guide

## PokerListings Privacy Policy

PokerListings.com respects your privacy. All information collected at this Web site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to PokerListings.com will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to.

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**  
PokerListings.com does not sell, rent, trade, loan, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including membership forms or e-mail lists.

**Browser information collected on the Web site:**  
PokerListings.com analyzes the Web site logs to improve the value of the materials available on our site. Our Web site logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals who actually browse the site.

**Advertisements:**  
We currently have ads served by an in-house program, which follows these privacy guidelines.

**Use of cookies:**  
PokerListings.com does use cookies on its Web site, mostly in order to track traffic coming from other Web sites and leaving to other Web sites. We do not use the cookies to attempt to link them with individuals to make any information personally identifiable.

**Use of Pixels:**  
PokerListings.com shares web site usage information about visitors to our web site, who have received a targeted promotional campaign, with a reputable third-party advertising company for the purpose of targeting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. For this purpose, we and our third-party advertising company note some of the pages you visit on our web site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). For more information about our third-party advertising company, please click here.

**Updates and changes:**  
PokerListings.com reserves the right to replace its Privacy Policy at any time. We suggest that you regularly check [Privacy Policy](https://www.pokerlistings.com/privacy-policy) for updates.

Please e-mail: info@pokerlistings.com with questions or comments.
